<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tel-Aviv Guide</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="events">Events</string>
    <string name="sites">Sites</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_tel_aviv">"Welcome to\nTel-Aviv"</string>
    <string name="visit_website">>Visit website</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="claro">Claro</string>
    <string name="mediterranean">Mediterranean</string>
    <string name="claro_address">Rav Aluf David Elazar St 30</string>
    <string name="claro_phone">+972 3-601-7777</string>
    <string name="claro_website">http://www.clarotlv.com/</string>
    <string name="claro_description">Beloved Tel Aviv chef Ran Shmueli has made Claro an homage to seasonal and local ingredients. Located in a restored Templer building, this spacious, light-­filled restaurant is a savvy choice for Mediterranean food. On weekends, order the family­-style platter composed of slow­-cooked lamb in a pomegranate sauce with sabzi (Persian fresh herbs), tzaziki, and hand­made pitas straight from the tabun.</string>
    <string name="hakosem">HaKosem</string>
    <string name="hakosem_address">Shlomo ha-Melekh St 1</string>
    <string name="hakosem_phone">+972 3-525-2033</string>
    <string name="hakosem_website">https://m.facebook.com/pages/%D7%94%D7%A7%D7%95%D7%A1%D7%9D/120889484655916</string>
    <string name="hakosem_description">Falafel can be found on just about every street corner in Tel Aviv, but Hakosem is in a league of its own, offering perfectly plump pita and deep­-fried balls of chickpea mash studded with fresh herbs, alongside impeccably fresh salads. Also try the hearty shawarma or the Iraqi breakfast known as sabich — wedges of fried potato, golden eggplant slices, hard­boiled eggs, and amba, a sunshine-yellow pickled mango sauce that seals the deal.</string>
    <string name="miznon">Miznon</string>
    <string name="miznon_address">Shlomo Ibn Gabirol St 23</string>
    <string name="miznon_phone">+972 3-716-8977</string>
    <string name="miznon_website">https://miznon.com/he/</string>
    <string name="miznon_description">Street food took a new turn when chef Eyal Shani opened this pita­-focused joint, a no­-frills spot that buzzes all day long. Fresh, fluffy pitas are packed with kebabs, steak and eggs, or ratatouille. Don’t pass up Shani’s signature dish: a full head of roasted cauliflower, which is rich, thick and filling — almost like a hunk of meat.</string>
    <string name="onza">Onza</string>
    <string name="onza_address">Rabbi Hannina St. 3</string>
    <string name="onza_phone">+972 3-648-6060</string>
    <string name="onza_description">Onza, a popular bar and restaurant located in the bustling Shuk HaPishpeshim (Jaffa’s flea market) added a Turkish touch to the menu when the talented chef pair Arik Darhani and Muli Magriso took reins of the kitchen towards the end of 2016. The menu features mezze like cacik, a Turkish yogurt dip made with cucumbers, mint, and dill; and pacanga borek, a pastry filled with pastirma (a Turkish cured beef) and kashkaval cheese served alongside a spicy grape leaf version of zhug (a hot sauce) and warm, comforting eggplant yogurt dip. Come early and browse the flea market for second-hand goodies and check out the shops that showcase local Israeli fashion.</string>
    <string name="onza_website">http://www.onza.co.il/he</string>
    <string name="jaffa_port">Jaffa Port</string>
    <string name="jaffa_port_address">Namal Yafo</string>
    <string name="jaffa_port_website">https://www.namalyafo.co.il/</string>
    <string name="jaffa_port_phone">03-6832255</string>
    <string name="jaffa_port_description">The revamped ancient Jaffa Port is where modernity meets history.  Jaffa Port, a renewed culinary, shopping and entertainment stop set in the city\'s ancient harbor, is home to various merchants and stalls that offer a vibrant and exciting experience inspired by the historical, cultural, and, of course, culinary legacy of its location. Take a stroll around the charming port, watch as elderly, weather-beaten fisherman hook calamari, stop off for an ice cream, or for a spot of live music at the Port’s Container bar. Jaffa Port Market combines traditional and ethnic elements with modern, urban touches. The 1,200 square metered area is set up like a race track, one path going through its entire length with shops, restaurants, galleries and booths on either side. Passageways peering into open-plan kitchens offer a carousel of tastes, smells and colors.</string>
    <string name="rothschild">Rothschild Boulevard</string>
    <string name="rothschild_address">sderot rothschild</string>
    <string name="rothschild_website">https://www.timeout.com/israel/attractions/a-stroll-down-rothschild-boulevard</string>
    <string name="rothschild_description">Wander down Tel Aviv’s most beautiful tree-lined boulevard and embrace the classic Bauhaus architecture. You’ll feel like the ultimate Tel Avivian. With everything from charming cafés, incredible ice cream parlours and lively late night clubs to historical museums, boutique hotels and endless charming places to sit and relax, Rothschild Boulevard is the perfect central Tel Aviv spot to explore. We’ve got the low-down on the must-see sights along the infamous street.</string>
    <string name="art_museum">Museum of Art</string>
    <string name="art_museum_address">27 Shaul HaMelech Blvd</string>
    <string name="art_museum_website">http://www.tamuseum.com/</string>
    <string name="art_museum_phone">03-6077020</string>
    <string name="art_museum_opening_hours">Mon, Wed, Sat 10:00-18:00; Tue, Thu 10:00-21:00; Fri 10:00-14:00</string>
    <string name="art_museum_price">NIS 50 (Adult), NIS 40 (TLV Resident/Student), NIS 25 (Senior/Soldier), Free (Children under 18)</string>
    <string name="art_museum_description"><![CDATA[The Tel Aviv Museum houses the best of Israeli art as well as new and old masters.  Gracing the walls of this museum are Israel’s most comprehensive collections of modern, contemporary, and Israeli art. The museum boasts an impressive collection of the old masters, diverse temporary exhibitions, displays of photography, design & architecture, a performance hall, and a beautiful, calming sculpture garden to wander around or relax in. When visiting, don’t miss the newest addition to the museum, the Herta and Paul Amir Building, which was designed by professor Preston Scott Cohen. Built around a spiraling, 90-foot high atrium, the Herta and Paul Amir Building is an architectural wonder. The interior space provides a unique setting for the display of contemporary art, a center for architecture, and a gallery.]]></string>
    <string name="sarona">Sarona Market</string>
    <string name="sarona_address">3 Aluf Kalman Magen</string>
    <string name="sarona_website">http://saronamarket.co.il/en</string>
    <string name="sarona_phone">03-6242424</string>
    <string name="sarona_opening_hours">Sun-Thu 09:00-23:00; Fri 08:00-18:00; Sat 09:00-23:00</string>
    <string name="sarona_description">One of Israel\'s largest indoor culinary offerings, Sarona Market features premium imported goods, alongside the best local fare.  Sarona Compound, a 140-year-old former Templar colony, is the first culinary center of its kind in Israel. An 8,700-square-meter market houses dozens of specialty food shops from all around the world. Inside the market, you’ll find everything imaginable from Dutch cheese to waffle towers and even Asian buns. Just outside the indoor market, dozens of clothing, book and shoe stores line its lanes, interspersed with lily ponds and grassy areas to relax.</string>
    <string name="promenade">Promenade</string>
    <string name="promenade_address">Tel Aviv Boardwalk Tourist Information Center, 46 Retsif Herbert Samuel St</string>
    <string name="promenade_phone">03-5166188</string>
    <string name="promenade_opening_hours">Tel Aviv Boardwalk Tourist Information Center open Daily until 17:30</string>
    <string name="promenade_website">https://www.visit-tel-aviv.com/</string>
    <string name="promenade_description">An amble down Tel Aviv’s promenade awakens all the senses with a feast of colors, sights and smells.  Nothing beats walking – or cycling – along the seaside promenade, breathing in the fresh, salty air of the Mediterranean. With Old Jaffa stamping the horizon to the south and the city’s skyscrapers to the north, it’s no wonder the Tel Aviv boardwalk is considered one of the world’s most beautiful. Sit on a bench and watch Tel Aviv life unfold before your eyes with beach-goers, paddle players and joggers doing their thing as the sounds of the waves gently crash on the shore.</string>
    <string name="white_noise">White Noise 2018</string>
    <string name="dance">Dance</string>
    <string name="white_noise_website">https://www.suzannedellal.org.il/</string>
    <string name="white_noise_phone">03-5105656</string>
    <string name="white_noise_venue">Suzanne Dellal Center</string>
    <string name="white_noise_address">5 Yahiel St, Neve Tzedek</string>
    <string name="white_noise_description">The Israeli Opera presents: Vertigo Dance Company and the Revolution Orchestra.  White Noise 2018 is a new adaptation of Noa Wertheim’s masterpiece, which was originally performed ten years ago. A decade back it received great praise in both Israel and abroad; in its new form–combining music and dance in a unique setting–the timeless piece is bound to receive equal praise as Wertheim peels back artistic layers to reveal new surprises. Her inspiration: Kalle Lasn’s acclaimed Culture Jam, a book that examines how America has traded in its status as a country to become a million-dollar brand. Similarly, Wertheimer is interested in the modern world, which she believes “produces a phenomenon of noises that penetrate the body\'s envelope and disrupt the systems of thought and rhythm of breathing.”</string>
    <string name="lollipop_fest">Lollipop Festival</string>
    <string name="music">Music</string>
    <string name="lollipop_fest_price">From 275 NIS</string>
    <string name="lollipop_fest_address">Rishon Lezion Live park</string>
    <string name="lollipop_fest_venue">Rishon Lezion Live park</string>
    <string name="lollipop_fest_website">http://www.tmisrael.co.il/event/JSOND/ALL/iw</string>
    <string name="lollipop_fest_description">Lollipop Festival lands to Israel with a first edition full of surprises, this summer 2018. One night of pop-immersion, with world super stars like Jason Derulo and Rita Ora, along with many other local and international artists  (Eliad Nahum, Axum and Adi Ulmansky). Tickets are on sale already from 275 NIS. The Lollipop festival is set to be one of the top events of the summer and will take place at Rishon Lezion Live park, at the outskirts of Tel Aviv, on August 1, 2018.</string>
    <string name="ringo">Ringo Starr</string>
    <string name="ringo_address">Menoarah Arena</string>
    <string name="ringo_venue">Menoarah Arena</string>
    <string name="ringo_website"><![CDATA[http://www.eventim.co.il/ringo-starr.html?affiliate=EIL&doc=artistPages/overview&fun=artist&action=overview&kuid=455997]]></string>
    <string name="ringo_description">Ringo Starr, the legendary drummer of The Beatles, is heading to Tel Aviv for his first show in Israel, in June 2018. Ringo Starr and The Beatles don’t need introduction, being music legends since the 60s. The Beatles had never performed in Israel during their career: a concert in the country was planned back in 1966, but unfortunately it never took place. Ringo Starr will perform in Israel with his band “All Starr”, as part of a European tour. Ringo Starr’s concert in Tel Aviv will take place at Menoarah Arena, on June 23, 2018.</string>
    <string name="purim">Purim Street Party</string>
    <string name="party">Party</string>
    <string name="purim_address">Kikar Hamedina</string>
    <string name="purim_venue">Kikar Hamedina</string>
    <string name="purim_description">The annual block party in the streets of Tel Aviv returns for Purim 2018. Perhaps the city’s biggest Purim party, this is the place where residents and visitors of all ages come to show off their Purim costumes.  The Purim Street Party will take place on March 2, 2018 in Kikar Hamedina (State Square) in northern Tel Aviv. The event usually begins at around 14:00 and continues through the afternoon. Entrance is totally free.</string>
    <string name="purim_price">Free</string>
    <string name="eurovision">Eurovision contest</string>
    <string name="eurovision_address">Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="eurovision_venue">Jerusalem</string>
    <string name="eurovision_description">The 2019 Eurovision Song Contest will take place in Israel in May. This will be the first time that Eurovision has been hosted in Israel for 20 years, and the location still has to be officially confirmed, though the likely venue will be Jerusalem at the Pais Arena or the Teddy Stadium. Eurovision in Israel will be a memorable event, with fans traveling to visit having to choose between staying in the host city itself, Jerusalem, with its uniquely rich history and culture, or the nearby (1 hour drive) liberal beach city of Tel Aviv with its world class nightlife.</string>
    <string name="eurovision_website">https://www.touristisrael.com/eurovision-song-contest-israel-jerusalem-may-2019/22200/</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="norman_hotel">The Norman</string>
    <string name="norman_address">23 Nachmani Street, Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="norman_description">Opened in 2014, The Norman was the first super-luxury boutique hotel in Tel Aviv. With its beautifully renovated 1920’s buildings and the charm of a by-gone era, this new hotel certainly did not disappoint. The first boutique hotel in the city to offer a swimming pool (this time, a rooftop pool), The Norman hosts two restaurants, one of which, Dinings Restaurant, is the Israeli sister of one of the most established eateries in London. Beautifully appointed and timelessly elegant, The Norman is a hotel that offers it all.</string>
    <string name="norman_phone">03-543-5555</string>
    <string name="norman_website">https://www.thenorman.com/</string>
    <string name="market_hotel_address">5 Beit Eshel Street, Jaffa, Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="market_hotel_phone">03-797-4000</string>
    <string name="market_hotel_description">Located just a few moments away from the Mediterranean Sea, the Market House Hotel is the first boutique hotel to open in the port of Jaffa. This charming hotel is set in a historic building which has been meticulously renovated. As the latest hotel from the Atlas group, guests can expect the usual Atlas hotel’s ‘happy hour’ every evening with free drinks and snacks for all guests to enjoy. For those looking for a boutique hotel in Tel Aviv that is in comparably different location to all other boutique hotels, the Market House is an excellent choice.</string>
    <string name="market_hotel_website">https://www.atlas.co.il/market-house-hotel-tel-aviv-israel</string>
    <string name="market_house_hotel">Market House Hotel</string>
    <string name="poli_hotel">The Poli House</string>
    <string name="poli_hotel_address">1 Nahalat Binyamin St, Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="poli_hotel_phone">03-710-5000</string>
    <string name="poli_hotel_description">The Poli House hotel is a fun, futuristic hotel with a striking design that sets it apart from the rest. The hotel was the vision of architect Karim Rashid and boasts a beautiful rooftop pool with 360-degree views of Tel Aviv. Each room features a walk-in shower, free Wi-Fi, and a complimentary minibar with yummy treats. The contemporary rooms boast bright colors mixed in with black and white furniture for added sophistication. And if you still have enough time after exploring the city, treat yourself to a luxury massage before plunging into the heated rooftop dinner.</string>
    <string name="poli_hotel_website">http://brownhotels.com/poli</string>
    <string name="white_villa_hotel">White Villa</string>
    <string name="white_villa_address">25 Ben Zion Boulevard, Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="white_villa_phone">03-602-8868</string>
    <string name="white_villa_decription">This quaint boutique hotel is set in a classically renovated villa that dates back to the Bauhaus period. The rooms here take their influence from sophisticated Italian design with white and wooden décor. There are only 18 rooms in the property so guests will receive an attentive and intimate service. A charismatic spiral staircase acts as the spine of the building, taking guests up through the two-floor property. There is also a pretty porch where breakfast is served each morning and guests who stay on the ground floor will benefit from their own private terrace. The White Villa is tucked away from the hustle and bustle of the city and is just a short walk from the popular areas off Dizengoff Center and Rothschild Boulevard.</string>
    <string name="white_villa_website">http://whitevillahotel.com/</string>
    <string name="cucu_hotel">CUCU Hotel</string>
    <string name="cucu_hotel_address">Dizengoff 83, Tel Aviv</string>
    <string name="cucu_hotel_descriptionb">Try a new addition to Tel Aviv’s design hotel scene with a visit to the CUCU Hotel. Located directly on Dizengoff Street, when staying here guests can expect to experience the best of the city’s thriving nightlife. With popular restaurants, bars, and shops literally on your doorstep, you will have time to enjoy one of the hotel’s spa treatments which include fabulous options for couples. This hotel is all about Israeli contemporary design and the rooms reflect this with bold furniture and large open spaces. This hotel is dedicated to providing a chilled out place to stay – something that will be truly welcomed after a long day of sightseeing.</string>
    <string name="cucu_hotel_phone">03-775-5777</string>
    <string name="cucu_hotel_website">https://www.cucuhotel.com/</string>
</resources>
